In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
I want to ask you to kill a man for me.
Kill a man?
Who?
The man who is next in line
to the throne of Midland...
...Count Julius.
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Noble Man
Julius...
I'm in luck.
Who is that kid?
Stand up, Adonis!
How shameful you are!
Were you really born of royal blood?
Now stand up!
Do not rest!
Your enemies never let you rest in battle!
Your Highness,
kindly call it a day for now...
Do not disturb us, Hassan!
Adonis will someday become...
...commander of the White Dragon
Knights, the land's strongest troop!
And that is not all!
It is even possible that he will marry
Lady Charlotte and rule all Midland!
Those who were born into royalty...
...must carry heavier burdens
than those who were not.
Such a burden is his destiny!
Fight on!
Let's see you try to take
at least one match from me!
So much for today.
Keep yourself warm and
be ready for tomorrow's training.
Master Adonis...
...you're quite injured.
I will treat your wounds.
Your father is desperate.
As your only parent, he's just trying
to raise you into a full-fledged knight.
You should not think ill of your father.
Sir Griffith, we have heard your story...
You protected the princess's
life with your own body...
How courageous you are!
Your words are too kind.
I am really no more than a coward.
Sir Griffith.
Oh, it's Lord Raban and Lord Owen.
That was a terrible affair
that occurred during the hunt.
Indeed. We nearly lost
a vital asset of Midland's army.
My life is nothing.
It is only important that
Princess Charlotte is safe from harm.
Oh, she has become even more charming.
She must be in love with someone.
Your Highness, please excuse my tongue.
However, your rigorous lessons have
become even more demanding of late.
I understand what you're going through...
...but you should be a little
easier on the young master.
I know.
Lately, I have had little success
with my duties in the royal court.
Due to such affairs,
I have become quite irritated.
I earnestly beg you not
to overextend yourself.
Is it the wind?
What?
A burglar?
I-I know you...
You are...
...Griffith's...
Excuse me...
B-Burglar?
He saw...
H-Hey...
What was that noise?
What is happening, Your Highness?
M-Master Adonis!
Who are you?
Let's go!
Burglar!
Don't let him get away!
What happened?
What's all this noise?
A burglar trespassed
upon His Highness's room!
I-It can't be!
Oh no...
How merciless this is...
After all he's been through, he never
once saw a father's smile of affection.
Mr. Hassan...
Find the burglar!
You must not let him
get out of the courtyard alive!
Yes, sir!
A sewer...
Find him!
He fell over here!
That sound...
I hear the sound of...
...swords in battle...
Gambino!
That's right...
I always desperately wanted
you to appreciate me.
Stop it!
I bet Griffith is enjoying
a succulent meal right about now.
There are a lot of perks that he can
enjoy at the princess's evening party.
He has nothing to worry about
except for the formalities!
By the way, where is Guts?
I haven't seen him since this morning.
I bet he is busy practicing
with his sword as always!
He is just slacking off!
Our two companies were
supposed to do joint drills today!
Without giving me any notice,
he never showed!
No need to get so furious...
Damn, she's scary!
Guts!
Guts, where have you been
running around all day long?
You caused us a lot
of trouble I'll have you know!
Do you really care about group unity?
Wait, is this an arrow wound?
Griffith...
...where is he?
Griffith is attending Lady Charlotte's
soirée in Promrose Palace.
I see...
Hey!
I'm not finished...
What's wrong with Guts?
Griffith...
I am a little tired...
Please have a seat here.
Thank you.
Wait!
Are you going there
in that shabby outfit?
Don't bring shame to Griffith.
You better wait until they finish
talking if you want to see him!
I'm borrowing this.
H-Hey...
In truth, I am not fond of soirées. They
are clamorous affairs, nothing more.
This one is being held to comfort
those who've fought tirelessly in battles.
But...
I think they should rather...
...stop the war itself than
hold a soirée like this one.
Why do most men commit
themselves to the affair of bloodshed?
You asked me such on
the hunting field, my lady.
Oh, yes...
Indeed, men may have
a barbarous side as you indicate.
However, it is...
...a tool to be used for both claiming
and protecting precious things.
It is a double-edged sword.
Precious things?
Such as family... or lovers?
For some men,
such things are duly cherished.
But there is one other thing more
precious to a man beyond all else...
Something one pursues for one's
own sake and not for that of any other.
A dream.
A dream...
Some dream of ruling the world...
...dedicating their entire life...
...to forging the perfect sword.
While some can be pursued
alone, some are like storms...
...blowing apart hundreds or
thousands of other dreams as they go.
A dream can fortify a man's life,
or it can bring suffering upon it.
A dream can make a man
feel alive, or it can kill him instead.
Even if a man
is abandoned by that dream...
...part of it will remain
smoldering in his heart.
Every man has envisioned
his life in this way, at least once.
A life as a martyr to his dream, his God.
To simply exist just
because one's been born...
...is the sort of notion
that I hate. I can't stand it.
I am sorry. I got carried away.
You must be getting bored.
O-Oh no...
I have never talked
with a man like this before...
I thought you were one of
the aristocracy when I first saw you.
You have so much command
for someone so young.
But on the hunting field, when you
taught me to whistle with a reed...
...you looked...
...like a child.
And now, you are like a philosopher,
enlightening me with your thoughts.
You are marvelous...
Your friends must be
fascinated by your charm too.
They are my able soldiers.
They are important comrades who
devote themselves to my dream.
However, they are not necessarily my friends.
In my eyes, a true friend is someone
who never clings to another's dream.
Someone independent...
...who can find his own reason to live
and follow that path without guidance.
And if anyone tries to crush his
dream, protect it heart and soul.
Even if that person happened to be me.
For me, a true friend...
...is someone whom I consider my equal.
You have great confidence in yourself.
That is exactly how I attained everything.
And now...
I am allowed to talk with you,
the princess of the kingdom.
Will you tell me your dream?
Princess!
Something awful has happened!
What ever is the matter?
Your uncle, Count Julius, has been killed!
That cannot be!
He was assassinated!
A burglar broke into his study and
even killed young Master Adonis...
The court has been thrown into an uproar.
What tremendous numbers...
Well, I've heard that the upcoming
battles could end the war.
I hope such a thing becomes reality.
No need to worry!
Midland's army has a guardian angel!
Speak of the devil...
Are you setting out?
Yes, Minister Foss.
We no longer have
General Julius. Only you are left.
You are now the guardian deity of
Midland. I pray for your good fortune...
...in battle.
That seems to be an exaggeration.
However, I shall exert myself to the utmost.
At any rate, I cannot bear
the news of the assassinations.
It is cruel that young Master Adonis
was killed. He was only a child.
Only a devil would do that.
No, it was not a devil's doing.
It was a man's doing, Minister.
By the way, Sir Griffith,
I happened to hear an odd rumor.
An odd rumor?
That the arrow aimed at
Lady Charlotte on the hunting field...
...could possibly have been aimed at you.
Could that be true?
Aiming at a humble unit commander?
According to the rumor...
...the assassin did not hail from
the Tudor Empire, but our own court.
A royal court, you see...
...is like a viper's nest
underneath its graceful facade.
It is no surprise that many people
are brewing up dark plots in the court.
My goodness...
For these people...
It is only a matter of killing a man
inside or outside the castle...
That is the only difference.
That is an interesting theory.
Well, then I will...
...strive to keep any unpleasantries
as far outside the court as possible.
Excuse me.
He did not even bat an eyelash!
Does that mean it was not his doing?
No, that cannot be.
If it were an accident,
it would be far too good to be true.
W-Wait, could it be that
he knows about me?
No, no man could discover my
intrigue, however keen he is.
Besides, there is no evidence left.
For me, a true friend...
...is someone whom I consider my equal.
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...